(Penny:)Why are you making this
so difficult?
(Leonard:)It's not difficult for me.
(Leonard:)I'm having fun.
(Man:)Leonard.
(Leonard:)What do you want me to do?
You started this.
(Leonard:)Do you want to go over
and tell him we're broken up?
(Raj:)No.
Well, then, what do you want?
(Wyatt:)I don't know.
(Leonard:)Don't you think that's something
you should
(Leonard:)have figured out
before you stomped over here?
(Howard:)Maybe.
(Sheldon:)Leonard, Penny, excellent.
(Sheldon:)I'd like to say I'm very happy
that you're back together,
(Sheldon:)and if I can figure out
a way to do so
(Sheldon:)and sound sincere, I will.
(Sheldon:)In the meantime,
(Sheldon:)I'd like to go over
some proposed changes
(Sheldon:)to the roommate agreement
specifically to address
(Sheldon:)Penny's annoying
personal habits.
(Penny:)Oh, my God.
(Penny:)What personal habits?
I have a list.
(Leonard:)FYI, overuse of the phrase
"Oh, my God" is number 12.
(Penny:)Okay, Sheldon,
you don't have to do this
(Penny:)because Leonard and I are not...
Ba-ba-ba-ba.
(Leonard:)Are you sure you want
to include him in this?
(Sheldon:)Include me in what?
(Sheldon:)Is there a plot afoot?
(Sheldon:)I'll have no
truck with plots.
(Penny:)No, you're right.
(Penny:)No, there's... there's no plots,
no trucks, no feet.